As a sales operations manager at Parch and Posey,
كمدير مبيعات في Parch &amp; Posey,
classifying orders into general groups is a helpful exercise.
فإن تصنيف الأوامر في مجموعات عامة تمرين مفيد.
But it's much more useful if you can let it count up all the orders in each group.
لكن سيكون مفيد أكثر إذا كان يمكنك أن تجعلها تعّد كل الأوامر في كل مجموعة.
Aggregating based on these new categories will make it
التجميع بناءً على هذه الفئات الجديدة يجعل
easier to report back to company leaders and take action.
إرسال التقارير إلى قيادات الشركة أسهل لاتخاذ الإجراءات.
The easiest way to count all the members of
أسهل طريقة لعّد كل الأعضاء في مجموعة
a group is to create a column that groups the way you want it to,
هي إنشاء عمود يجمع بالطريقة التي تريدها،
then create another column to count by that group.
ثم إنشاء عمود آخر يعّد بهذه المجموعة.
Here, we're using CASE to group orders into those with total quantity sold over 500,
هنا، نستخدم CASE لتجميع الأوامر إلى هذه التي إجمالي المُباع فيها يتخطى 500،
and those with 500 or less.
وتلك التي بها 500 أو أقل.
This query is an excellent place to use numbers
هذا الاستعلام مكان ممتاز لاستخدام الأرقام
instead of full column calculation in the GROUP BY clause,
بدلاً من احتساب عمود كامل في رابط GROUP BY،
because repeating the CASE statement in
ولأن تكرار عبارة CASE في
the GROUP BY would make the query obnoxiously long.
GROUP BY قد يجعل الاستعلام طويل بشكل سيء.
Now, you might be thinking,
الآن، قد تتساءل،
why wouldn't I just use a WHERE clause to filter out rows I don't want to count?
لماذا لا نستخدم رابط WHERE لتصفية الصفوف التي لا أريد عدّها؟
You could do that,
يمكنك فعل ذلك،
and it would look like this.
وستظهر هكذا.
This would be tedious if we had a number of different cases.
وسيكون هذا مملاً إذا كان لدينا الكثير من الحالات المختلفة.
We would need a separate query for each one.
سنحتاج استعلام منفصل لكل واحدة.